{
    "classes":[
	{
	    "name":"Spring 2017",
	    "_id":"123456789",
	    "student signup code":"abcdef",
	    "active":"true",
	    "students":[
	    {
		"firstName":"alex",
		"lastName":"luken",
		"_id":"stu1",
		"password":"abc123",
		"salt":"jack",
		"homework":[
		    {
			"name":"first vocab",
			"_id":"1hw",
			"endingMessage":"Congratulations you finished it",
			"timestampStart":"2012-04-23T18:25:43.511Z",
			"timestampEnd":"2012-04-23T18:28:43.511Z",		    
			"grade":"1/2",
			"questions":[
			    {
				"type":"mc",
				"prompt":"What is the latin word for you",
				"correct":"tu",
				"options":[
				    "tu",
				    "eres",
				    "what"
				],
				"studentResponse":"tu"
			    },
			    {
				"type":"fb",
				"prompt":"What is the term for a type of grammar that describes place",
				"correct":"preposition",
				"options":[
				],
				"studentResponse":"asdf"
			    }
			]
		    },
		    {
			"name":"second vocab",
			"_id":"2hw",
			"endingMessage":"Congratulations you finished the second assignment",
			"timestampStart":"2012-04-24T18:25:43.511Z",
			"timestampEnd":"2012-04-24T18:28:43.511Z",		    
			"grade":"1/2",
			"questions":[
			    {
				"type":"la",
				"prompt":"What are you confused about",
				"correct":"",
				"options":[
				]
			    },
			    {
				"type":"ma",
				"prompt":"What are terms for grammar",
				"correct":["preposition","noun","verb"],
				"options":[
				    "preposition",
				    "noun",
				    "verb",
				    "alex"
				],
				"studentResponse":["alex"]
			    }
			]
		    }
		]
	    },
	    {
		"firstName":"tim",
		"lastName":"Mains",
		"_id":"stu2",
		"password":"qwer",
		"salt":"jack",
		"homework":[
		    {
			"endingMessage":"Congratulations you finished it",
			"timestampStart":"2012-04-24T18:25:43.511Z",
			"timestampEnd":"2012-04-24T18:28:43.511Z",		    
			"name":"third vocab",
			"grade":"1/2",
			"_id":"3hw",
			"questions":[
			    {
				"type":"tf",
				"prompt":"Alex is amazing at latin",
				"correct":"f",
				"options":[
				],
				"studentResponse":"f"
			    },
			    {
				"type":"fb",
				"prompt":"What is the term for a type of grammar that is a thing",
				"correct":"noun",
				"options":[
				],
				"studentResponse":"alex"
			    }
			]
		    },
		    {
			"name":"fourth vocab",
			"_id":"4hw",
			"endingMessage":"good for you",
			"grade":"1/2",
			"timestampStart":"2012-04-25T18:25:43.511Z",
			"timestampEnd":"2012-04-25T18:28:43.511Z",		    
			"questions":[
			    {
				"type":"la",
				"prompt":"What else are you confused about",
				"correct":"",
				"options":[
				],
				"studentResponse":"fudge sickle"
			    },
			    {
				"type":"ma",
				"prompt":"What are good adjectives",
				"correct":["fast","slow"],
				"options":[
				    "fast",
				    "slow",
				    "dumb",
				    "stupid"
				],
				"studentResponse":["alex","slow"]
			    }
			]
		    }
		]
	    }
	],
	"chapters":[
	    {
		"name":"section 1",
		"order":"1",
		"_id":"ch1",
		"homework":[
		    {
			"name":"first vocab",
			"_id":"1hw",
			"endingMessage":"Congratulations you finished it",
			"questions":[
			    {
				"type":"mc",
				"prompt":"What is the latin word for you",
				"correct":"tu",
				"options":[
				    "tu",
				    "eres",
				    "what"
				]
			    },
			    {
				"type":"fb",
				"prompt":"What is the term for a type of grammar that describes place",
				"correct":"preposition",
				"options":[
				]
			}
			]
		    },
		    {
			"name":"second vocab",
			"_id":"2hw",
			"endingMessage":"Congratulations you finished the second assignment",
			"questions":[
			    {
				"type":"la",
				"prompt":"What are you confused about",
				"correct":"",
				"options":[
				]
			    },
			    {
				"type":"ma",
				"prompt":"What are terms for grammar",
				"correct":["preposition","noun","verb"],
				"options":[
				    "preposition",
				    "noun",
				    "verb",
				    "alex"
				]
			    }
			]
		    }
		]
	    },
	    {
		"name":"section 2",
		"order":"1",
		"_id":"ch2",
		"homework":[
		    {
			"name":"third vocab",
			"_id":"3hw",
			"endingMessage":"Nice job",
			"questions":[
			    {
				"type":"tf",
				"prompt":"Alex is amazing at latin",
				"correct":"f",
				"options":[
				]
			    },
			    {
				"type":"fb",
				"prompt":"What is the term for a type of grammar that is a thing",
				"correct":"noun",
				"options":[
				]
			    }
			]
		    },
		    {
			"name":"fourth vocab",
			"_id":"4hw",
			"endingMessage":"good for you",
			"questions":[
			    {
				"type":"la",
				"prompt":"What else are you confused about",
				"correct":"",
				"options":[
				]
			    },
			    {
				"type":"ma",
				"prompt":"What are good adjectives",
				"correct":["fast","slow"],
				"options":[
				    "fast",
				    "slow",
				    "dumb",
				    "stupid"
				]
			    }
			]
		    }
		]
	    }
	]
	}
    ]

}
